好了 我出门了
Okay. I'm taking off.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我们不是约好要让那只鸡度过
I thought we were going to give a chicken
生命中最美好的一天吗
the best day of its life.
我也不想总是改时间
I hate that we keep rescheduling that,
可是当地产经纪人就得周末上班
but being a realtor man means working on sundays,
就像神父和莱斯利·斯塔尔一样
like priests and Lesley Stahl.
祝你好运 亲爱的
Good luck out there, honey.
我们都指着你了
We're all counting on you.
希望能成功到达那里
Just got to make it through this commute.
到了会告诉你的
I'll call when I get there.
我到了
I'm there!
祝你愉快
Have a great day!
我在帮我们的邻居杰瑞卖房子
I am handling the sale of our neighbor Jerry's house.
他要卖了房子搬去单身公寓
He's selling it and moving into a bachelor pad
因为他已经正式离婚了
now that he's officially divorced.
这太棒了
Which is great!
我没觉得很棒
Well, I don't know about "great."
可能的确来去自由一些
I mean, you can come and go as you please, I suppose,
也许还能和送快递的姑娘调调情
and maybe see what's up with the U.P.S. girl
她总是会问你是否健身
who's always asking if you work out, or --
这很棒是因为我们居然有机会
It's great because we have the rare opportunity
选择我们的新邻居
to choose our new neighbors.
当然同时还要
While still looking out
兼顾我客户的利益
for my client's best interests, of course.
你懂的
Winkwink.
我现在处境有点微妙
I'm in kind of in a delicate spot --
夹在老婆和隔壁的哥们之间左右为难
stuck between my wife and the guy next door,
不过我有把握同时满足他们两个
but I'm pretty sure I can satisfy them both simultaneously.
好了 他们来了 他们来了
Okay. That's them. That's them.
所有人都装成做园艺的样子
Everybody look like you're gardening.
卢克 拿起那把小锄头
Luke, grab that little hoe.
她说的不是那个意思
Uh, I -- I don't think that's what she meant.
对吧
Is it?
我们为什么要这么做
Okay, why are we doing this?
这是他们第三次来了 我们要表现好点
This is their third visit, and we want to look good.
他们有什么好的
What's so great about them?
他们在原来的社区很受欢迎
They're very well-liked in their neighborhood,
他们的孩子很懂礼貌
they have very polite children,
他们很有深度
and they are sophisticated.
那个男的收藏了很多红酒
The husband is a huge wine collector.
这才是重点
Oh, there it is.
好了 快点 快点
All right, this is it. This is it.
看着精神点儿
Okay, look sharp.
卢克 你脸上是什么
Luke, what's on your face?
我不知道 什么颜色的
I don't know. What color is it?
怎么弄不下来
Why isn't it coming off?
这种行为太奇怪了
This feels like a panic move.
你们好
Hey... again. Hello.
-早安 -你们好
- Morning. - Hello.
家庭园艺时间
Just doing a little family gardening.
回见
See ya.
顺便说一句那是花生酱
It's peanut butter, by the way.
可两天前花生酱就吃光了
We ran out of peanut butter two days ago.
我的神哪 管用了
Holy cow. It works!
他在干嘛
What is he doing?
他把袜子放进汽水包装里再拿出来
He's putting socks in a soda box and pulling them out.
不
Oh, no.
这和我祖母那时开始
This is like when my grandmother
用仙人掌梳头发一样
started combing her hair with a cactus.
杰 杰 总统是谁
Jay, Jay, who is the president?
这玩意儿能让我当上总统
I will be when they see this.
瞧瞧这个
Check this out.
我在卧室里最大的难题是什么
What's my biggest problem in the bedroom?
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
我总是穿同一双袜子
It's that I'm always wearing the same socks
因为它们总是在最上面
Because they're always up front.
但是这玩意能存放并轮换袜子
But this bad boy stores and rotates your socks.
这将创造衣柜界的历史
It's gonna revolutionize the closet industry.
我真是生在一个黄金时代
What an exciting time to be alive.
我得找律师聊聊
I'm gonna get my lawyer on the horn,
早点把名字的专利申请下来
try to lock the name down.
这个怎么样
Check this --
"袜掘机"
"Sock it to me."
"袜袜机器"怎么样
How about "Soxbox?"
歌洛莉亚 拜托
Gloria, please.
我是要推崇一种生活方式
I'm selling a lifestyle here.
妈 我们去泳池那玩
Uh, Mom, we're gonna go head out by the pool.
不不不 等等 打个招呼
No, no, no, wait. Say hello.
杰 这是索菲
Jay, this is Sophie.
你好
Hello.
你好 普里契特先生
Hi, Mr. Pritchett.
那是什么 自动配袜机吗
What's that? Some sort of sock dispenser?
没错 我是做衣柜生意的
Bingo! I'm in the closet business.
这是我的新发明的雏形
And this is a crude prototype of my new invention.
这创意真棒
What a great idea.
它能帮你替换袜子
You rotate your socks
这样就不会一直穿同一双了
so you don't keep wearing the same ones.
完全正确
That's exactly right.
我叫它"袜掘机"
I call it "Sock it to me."
这名字真妙
That's so clever.
很幽默 还说明了它的功能
It's funny, and it tells you what it does.
想象一下用胡桃木做的样子
Imagine it in walnut.
这怎么回事
What's happening?
我很抱歉他这么无聊
I -- I am so sorry that he's boring you.
不 我对这些很感兴趣
No, I like this sort of stuff.
我爷爷厄尔也是做衣柜生意的
My grandpa Earl's in the closet business, too.
等等 厄尔
Wait, wait. Earl?
不会是厄尔·钱伯斯吧
Not -- not Earl Chambers.
对 他拥有"衣柜衣柜衣柜...
Yeah, he owns closets, closets, closets...
衣柜"公司 我知道
Closets. Yeah.
我认识你爷爷
I know your grandpa.
1980年
It was 1980.
厄尔和我合办了"衣橱福尼亚"公司
Earl and I had just formed our company, Closet-Fornia.
生意很不错 高端客户
Business was great, high-end clients,
还有一两个名流光顾
maybe a celebrity or two.
不过我不方便说出他们的名字
I shouldn't name names. Anyway...
有一天我上班的时候
Came to work one day,
发现厄尔的桌子被清空了
and earl's desk had been cleared out.
他对我们一半的客户说了我的坏话
He had badmouthed me to half our rolodex.
我都绝望了
It was devastating.
我只能重新开始
I had to start all over.
算了 告诉你们吧
Well, what the hell?
拉里·哈格曼曾是我们的客户
It was Larry Hagman.
那家伙很棒
Heck of a guy.
胸怀宽广似海洋
Heart as big as his hat.
这么快就回来了
Hey, you're back already?
生日派对怎么样
How was the birthday party?
我骑了一头独角兽
I rode a unicorn.
对 没错
Yes, you did.
自己一个人骑上去的
All by your lonesome.
不是真的独角兽
It wasn't a real unicorn.
多谢解释
Thank you.
我准备去做作业了
I'm gonna go and do homework.
不是紧急事情别来烦我
Don't knock unless it's an actual emergency.
比如打蜘蛛什么的
Not a spider.
普兰克老师周末还留作业吗
Ms. Plank gave her homework on the weekend?
她才七岁
She's 7.
我知道 那女人疯了
I know. The woman is insane.
不过听着
But listen.
我在荧光纹身贴那里排队时听到了些消息
I heard something in the glitter-tattoo line.
什么
What?
斯帕萝老师的班上有了一个空位
There's an opening in Miss Sparrow's class.
天哪 小卡 那太棒了
Oh, my god! Cam, that's amazing.
我们必须把她换到那个班上
We got to get her in.
我知道 明天一早我们就去帮她换班
I know. We're going in first thing tomorrow.
给我看看你纹了什么
Let's see it.
两只海豚组成的红心
Two dolphins that form a heart.
莉莉的学校有两位二年级老师
There are two second-grade teachers at Lily's school --
斯帕萝老师
Miss Sparrow,
她的课有趣而刺激
who makes learning fun and adventurous.
以及教莉莉的普兰克老师
And then there's Lily's teacher, Mrs. Plank,
她快把莉莉逼疯了
who is stressing Lily out.
让我们看看 宝贝
Let's see, sweetie.
做得真棒
Good job.
不 我把蝌蚪拼错了
Oh, no! I spelled "Tadpole" wrong!
没关系 只是个小错误而已
Oh, well, now, that's just one mistake.
普兰克老师不允许有错误
Mrs. Plank doesn't tolerate mistakes!
-好吧 -好吧
- Okay. - All right.
我称普兰克老师为"可烂老师"
I call Mrs. Plank "Mrs. Crank."
因为
Because, you know,
我有勇气说出别人不敢说的
I have the courage to say what others won't.
背着她说
Behind her back.
我一年前帮上一个房主
And I also helped the previous owners
装了全新的即热式热水系统
install a brand-new tankless water heater a year ago,
但是他们有感激我吗
but did they show any gratitude?
没有
Nope!
因为这工作"不用谢"[谐音]
Because it's a "Tankless" job.
没错
Yes!
搬过来吧
Please move in.
我们可以经常这么即兴创作段子
We can riff like this all the time.
你们觉得怎么样 还喜欢吗
So, what do ya think? Do you still love it?
当然
Absolutely.
我已经在想象在院子里种满鲜花
I can just see filling this yard with flowers.
和我们假装在干的一样
Just like we're pretending to do.
话说我很喜欢你的鞋子
By the way, I love those shoes.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
乔治的公司在为大概十家鞋子品牌做公关
George's firm does P.R. for about 10 shoe brands.
如果我们搬进来
If we end up living here,
相信我 你们会被淹没在鞋子的海洋
trust me, you'll be swimming in shoes.
我做过这个梦
I've had that dream.
说起梦想 你们怎么想
Speaking of dreams, what do you think?
准备好提笔签约了吗
You guys ready to pull the trigger?
我想准备好了
I think we are.
-棒极了 -太好了
- That's great! - Yes!
我穿六号鞋
I'm a size 6!
自从上次我从房顶上掉下来
Not since I fell off the roof
刚好摔在正被送来的蹦床上
while they were delivering our trampoline
就再没发生过这么美好的事了
have things come together so beautifully.
再见
See you soon!
成功了
We did it.
我们就要迎来史上最棒的邻居了
We are gonna have the best neighbors ever!
这什么声音
What's that noise?
酷
Cool!
我才不想看什么破房子
I don't want to see a stupid house.
你能不能闭上嘴别丢我们的脸
Hey, how 'bout you shut up and not embarrass us?
你俩能不能都闭嘴
How 'bout you both shut up?
听你们说话都听烦了
I'm sick of listening to you.
别这么跟你爸说话
Hey, don't talk to your dad like that,
不然就搬去跟你男友住
or you can go live with your boyfriend.
他不是我男友
He's not my boyfriend.
我只是跟他亲热而已
I just make out with him
这样就不用再上他的课了
so I don't have to take his class again.
我们该去打个招呼
We should go say hi.
不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
菲尔 快摘下来
Phil, shut it down.
我在努力 这东西怎么这么结实
I'm trying! What are these things made of?
快点
Come on.
天啊
Dude...
我爱死这地方了
I love this place.
我也是 亲爱的
Me too, baby.
我一直想住在西班牙式的房子里
I always wanted a Spanish house.
就好像住在小公牛墨西哥餐厅一样
It'll be like living at an El Torito.
是你家人
Oh! Your family.
你们是邻居吗 喜欢这地方吗
Hey, you the neighbors? You like living here?!
你说什么 不好意思
What? I'm so sorry.
交通噪音太大 我听不清
It's so hard to hear over all that freeway noise, right?
这样就不会有人抱怨
Hey, then no one's gonna complain
我驾驶汽车 机车和我老婆时的噪音了
when I'm revving my cars, my bike, or my lady.
我叫罗尼·拉方丹
I'm Ronnie Lafontaine.
这位辣妹是我老婆 安布尔
And this hot lady right here is my wife, Amber.
这两个小恶魔是塔米和小罗尼
And these two little hellraisers are Tammy and Ronnie jr.
你好啊 辣妹
Hey, hot stuff.
我 我 我吗
M-m-m-me?
你好啊
Um...hello.
这地方太好了
Damn, this neighborhood's sweet.
离我工作的地方也很近
Yeah, it's close to my work, too.
你是干什么工作的 罗尼
Wh-- uh, what is your line of work, Ronnie?
我基本上算是医生
Well, I'm basically a doctor.
别谦虚了
Oh, stop being modest.
他有一大堆医用大麻药房
He owns, like, a buttload of medical-weed dispensaries.
我就说我看你怎么这么眼... 你好
Ah, that's where I kno-- Oh, hello?
大妹子 你好像不太舒服
Honey, you look a little nauseous.
是啊 是有点
Yeah. Yeah, a little.
我有东西能让你舒坦些
Hey, I got something for that.
不用了
All good.
你怎么能把她领家里来
How could you bring her to my home?
她是我的死敌的孙女
She's the granddaughter of my worst enemy.
我又不知道是这样
I had no idea who she was.
我是在戏剧小组认识她的
I met her in my theater group.
我演凯撒 她演3号小妾
I'm Caesar, and she's Concubine #3.
缘由天定躲不掉
It was bound to happen.
厄尔·钱伯斯是个在背后暗算人的骗子
Earl Chambers is a liar and a backstabber
他背叛了我却从未道歉
who betrayed me and never apologized.
杰 拜托 不就是衣柜吗
Jay, please. It's just closets.
我倒希望是"就是衣柜"公司的人
I wish it was just closets.
那帮人还值得我尊敬
I respect those guys.
糟了 她看到我的"袜掘机"了
Damn it, she saw the Sock It To Me!
那又怎样
So what?
如果她能记得它的工作原理
If she can remember how it works,
她会一五一十地告诉厄尔的
She's gonna tell Earl all about it.
她会记得它的工作原理
If she can remember how it works?
不就是把袜子放到盒子里
You put the sock in a box.
连乔都能想得出来
Even Joe could have thought of that.
你还跟她说过什么
What else did you discuss with her?
你提到过
Did you mention
我们在实验发光晾衣杆的事吗
we've been experimenting with lighted hanging rods?
我不太擅长和女生聊天
I don't have a great rap with girls,
可我不会傻到聊那个
but it's better than that.
那你只能和别人聊了
Well, you're gonna use it with someone else
因为我禁止你再见她
'cause I forbid you to see her.
-什么 -这不公平
- What? - That's not fair.
不公平的是在我重拾生活的同时
What's not fair is me picking up the pieces of my life
厄尔却可以出演《豪门恩怨》
while Earl gets to be an extra on "Dallas"!
邓菲
Hey, Dunphy.
我在打量这棵树
Just checking out this tree.
是啊
Oh, yeah,
乱透了 是吧
it's really messy, right?
把房子的光都挡住了
And it makes the house so dark.
不过那些老鼠挺喜欢的
But the -- the rats love it, so...
别担心 我会把它砍掉的
Yeah, no worries. I'm gonna cut it down.
我可不想让树液滴到我的躺椅上
I don't want all this sap all over my lawn couch.
我要是你就不会先急着砍树 罗尼
Well, I wouldn't fire up your chainsaw just yet, Ronnie.
房地产市场竞争很激烈
It's a very competitive market.
还有别的买家吗
Is there another buyer?
我不能告诉你
I really shouldn't say.
你这是 在玩地产经纪人的花招吗
Is this -- is this one of those realtor tricks?
不是
No.
你是想用这种方法让我提价吗
Where you're trying to get me to raise my offer?
不是
Oh, no.
很可惜它奏效了
Well, it's working.
这样吧 我再加五万
All right. I'll throw in another 50 grand.
什么 这主意糟透了
What?! That's a terrible idea!
我不能错过这房子
I'm not losing the house.
我在里面干了人生最爽的一炮
I had the best sex of my life in there.
什么时候干的
When?!
打扰了 可烂老师
Excuse me, Ms. Crank.
普兰克 普兰克老师
-Plank. Ms. Plank?
什么事
Yes?
你好 是个哭脸印章啊
Hi. I-- Oh. A frowny-face stamp.
我都不知道还有这玩意
I didn't know they made those.
我是从德国特别订做的
I had to special order it from Germany.
你们有什么事
May I help you?
我们是莉莉的家长
Uh, well, we're Lily's parents.
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
也算不上是问题
Not so much a problem, no.
是啊 更像是给您一个机会...
No, more of an opportunity for you to...
减轻工作负担
lighten your workload.
也许能让哭脸印章倒过来
Maybe turn that frowny-face stamp upside down.
让我猜猜
Let me guess--
你们听说了
you've heard there's
年轻的斯帕萝老师的班上有空位了
an opening in young Ms. Sparrow's classroom.
-什么 -哪个老师
- What? - Miss who?
-是那个 你确定 -有空缺
- Is this-- Do you-- - An opening?
没听说
No.
不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
请原谅我妄下结论
Forgive me for jumping to conclusions.
请你们告诉我你们有何贵干
By all means, tell me why you're here.
我们 我们就是顺路
Well, we-- we've just, uh, stopped by,
过来一趟
Uh, in the neighborhood to
-打个招呼 -问个好 你好
- say hello. - Say hi. Hi.
另外...
And, also, um...
有关您推荐给莉莉的
about this opening in Miss Sparrow's class
斯帕萝老师的班
that you suggested for Lily.
您觉得这事...
Is that something that you would...
您觉得这主意好吗
That you would think would be a good idea?
家长无权
Parents are not allowed
给孩子选择老师
to choose their children's teachers.
当然了
No, and, of course,
我肯定不会为莉莉要求特殊对待
I would never suggest special treatment for Lily
尽管她曾是孤儿 又是外国移民
even if she is a -- a former orphan and minority
还是两个同志的女儿
and-- and daughter of two gay men.
对她来说可是一大负担
That's a big load on those little shoulders.
你们的意思是你们女儿处于不利
Are you suggesting that your daughter is at a disadvantage
因为她是被同志家庭养大的吗
because she's being raised by gay parents?
这能打动您吗
Is it working?
好吧 说实话
Okay. You know what?
我们只不过觉得莉莉不太接受
Look. Uh, we just don't think that Lily responds
您的教学方法
to your, uh, teaching methods,
我们觉得她在斯帕萝老师的课上会更开心
and we think she would be happier in Miss Sparrow's class.
在那个被她
We would all be happier
称为教室的游乐场里我们都会更开心的
in that new-age drum circle she calls a classroom.
好吧 我们无意冒犯
Okay, well, we didn't mean to offend you.
我们不是说你比她的差
We're not saying you're any worse than her.
比她差
She.
您说什么
Ma'am?
比她差
"Than she."
这才是正确的语法
That's proper English.
真遗憾莉莉学不到了
It's too bad Lily won't learn it.
所以她能去咯
So she can go.
据我所知 她已经去了
As far as I'm concerned, she's gone already.
又一个落在后面的小孩
One more child left behind.
知道吗 不 莉莉会很好的
Okay, you know what? No. Lily will be fine,
因为她会在一个更有爱的环境里
'cause she's gonna have the chance to thrive
有蓬勃发展的机会
in a more supportive environment.
是啊 你没必要担心她
Yeah, you don't need to worry about she.
来这里真是个好主意 歌洛莉亚
This place is a great idea, Gloria.
我跟你说过吗
Did I ever tell you
我就是在这里第一次吃了椒盐卷饼面包
this is where I first tried pretzel bread?
你好 杰
Hello, Jay.
你好 厄尔
Hello, Earl.
我邀请了他
I invited him
好让你们能放下彼此间过去的矛盾
so that you two finally can bury the machete.
这个人渣曾在背后给过我一"矛"
Well, this scumbag already buried it in my back.
你个王八蛋
You son of a bitch!
别这样 别这样
No! No! No! No!
住手 坐下来
Stop it! Sit down!
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
你俩得成为朋友
You two need to be friends.
世界上只有你们两个人
You're the only two people in the world
这么在意衣柜
that care so much about closets.
这太愚蠢了
This is silly!
那些摆放着
I guess those angled shelves
你的宝贝鞋子的架子才愚蠢
that display all your precious shoes are silly.
或者旋转领带架子
Or the rotating tie rack
那能帮脑外科医生节约珍贵的时间
that helps a brain surgeon save valuable seconds,
也许救下一条人命
and, just maybe, a life.
你当时对我步步阻挠
You fought me every step of the way on that.
因为科技还没发展到那种地步
Because the technology wasn't there yet.
人们会受伤的
People were gonna get hurt!
-如果你能听听 -够了
- If you would open your ears -- - Enough!
你俩表现得像小孩子一样
You two are acting like two little boys.
所以我要用我妈妈对付
So I'm gonna have to handle this
我的两个弟弟的方法来对你们
how my mother handled my two brothers.
你俩要么解决这事
It's either you two work this out...
要么杀了对方
...or you kill each other.
当疯狂的大麻毒贩提高报价时
When Reefer Madness raised his offer,
我们邀请了汤普森夫妇过来
we invited the Thompsons over
试图说服他们也提高报价
to try to convince them to raise theirs.
我们想向他们展示
We wanted to show them
那所房子的最大优点
that the best thing about that house
就是它的位置
is its location.
它位于邓菲家旁边
It's Dunphy-adjacent.
今晚过得很开心
That was so much fun.
你们很快会给我们答复吧
We'll hear from you soon, huh?
当然啦
You sure will.
比你想象的更快
Sooner than you think.
-好吧 -再见
- All right. - Okay, bye.
-小心开车 -回头见
- Drive safe. - See ya.
搞定了
Nailed it.
他们走了吗
Are they gone?
是啊 但是别担心
They are, but don't you worry.
我们很快就会经常见到他们了
We are gonna see a lot more of those two soon.
更快收到了他们的消息
Oh, and hearing from them even sooner.
看来某人意犹未尽啊
It looks like someone didn't get their "Phil" of Dunphy.
不好
No.
什么
What?
他们撤回报价了
They pulled their offer.
为什么 出什么事了
Why? What happened?
你们两个变态可能吓坏他们了
You pervs probably freaked 'em out.
你说变态是什么意思
What do you mean, "Pervs"?
就是变态色情狂的简称
It's short for perverts.
你们整晚都在对他们投怀送抱
You guys were throwing yourselves at them all night long.
我能怎么说 卖鞋子就是那样的
What can I say? That's shoe business.
进家里可不能带枪
Whoa, no guns allowed in this house.
脱了上衣吧 丽莎
Let's off that top, Lisa.
我是说 我给你加点酒吧 丽莎
Let's... let's top that off, Lisa.
菲尔
Phil.
这很有趣
So, this has been fun.
等你们搬过来后会更有趣的
It'll be even more fun when you guys move in.
就算我们提高报价
Well, even if we raise our offer,
谁知道我们能不能买到这房子
who knows if we'll get the house?
幸运的是
Fortunately,
你们找对了人[跟对的人上了床]
you are getting into bed with the right people.
当然 我们不做不得体的事
Nothing inappropriate, of course.
你懂的
Wink, wink.
但不要误会了
But just so there's no misunderstanding,
我们想要你们
we want you.
你为什么不阻止我们
Why didn't you stop us?
我又不知道你们想干什么
Hey, I don't know what you guys are into.
天啊 我们要怎么做
Oh, my god. What are we gonna do?
放轻松啦
Oh, relax.
我敢肯定你们会找到
I'm sure you guys will find a couple
想和你们交往的夫妇
that wants to get with you.
我来这里是因为她说你想道歉
I'm here because she says you want to apologize.
是你该向我道歉
You're the one that owes the apology to me.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
1998年的橱柜大会
ClosetCon, 1998.
你毁了我的摊位
You sabotaged my booth.
那玩意儿倒了 因为它很廉价
That thing collapsed because it was cheap
而且是在东方买的 和你老婆一样
and bought in the orient -- like your wife.
我说了多少次了
How many times do I have to tell people --
见面是需要付钱
You only pay for the meeting.
但有真感情才能结婚
The feelings have to be real!
别让你孙女再来我们家
Just keep your granddaughter out of my house.
我推测一定是你派她过来打探
For all I know, you sent her over there to spy on me!
索菲吗 她去你家干什么
Sophie? What is she doing at your house?
跟我儿子约会
Dating my kid.
米奇尔吗 他都有四十岁了
Mitchell? He's got to be 40 years old.
你不知道吗 我必须告诉你了
And don't you know that -- oh, I get to do this.
米奇尔是基佬
Mitchell is gay.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我继子曼尼
My stepson, Manny.
她在跟你的儿子约会吗
She's dating one of you?
我可爱的小索菲
My little, sweet Sophie?
没错
That's right.
我儿子在跟她约会
My boy's dating her.
他在认真跟她约会
He's dating her real good.
我要结束这一切
Well, I'm gonna put an end to it.
好主意 厄尔
Great idea, Earl.
因为女孩们就喜欢
'Cause girls love take advice
从爷爷那听取关于男生的建议
from their grandfathers about boys.
我搞了你前妻
I banged your ex-wife!
如果你搞了迪迪 我的确该向你道歉
If you banged Dede, I do owe you an apology.
莉莉 是大爸二爸 能跟你聊聊吗
Lily, it's daddies. Can we talk to you?
好吧 蜘蛛在哪
All right. Where's the spider?
不不 不是那么回事
No, no, no, it's -- it's not that.
听着 我们有好消息
Now, listen, we have some good news.
我们知道你在学校压力很大
We -- we know you've been stressed out at school,
所以大爸和我今天去了学校
so daddy and I went down there today,
我们帮你换到了
and we got you into...
斯帕萝老师的班级
Miss Sparrow's class!
-没搞错吧 -我还以为你是想让我说
- Really? - I thought you were setting me up.
但我想留在普兰克老师的班里
But I want to stay with Mrs. Plank.
为什么啊 斯帕萝老师幽默又有创意
But why? Miss -- Miss Sparrow's so fun and creative.
今天 她给了我们纱线
Yeah, today, she gave us yarn,
我们想做什么都行
and we did whatever we wanted.
我可不想玩纱线
I don't want to play with yarn.
我想阅读 学数学
I want to read and learn math.
我们也学数学
We do math.
是吗 2加7等于几
Really? What's 2 plus 7?
不 是9
No. No, it's 9.
但那是无心之过 亲爱的
But that's an honest mistake, sweetheart.
那蓝色和黄色混在一起是什么颜色
Okay, what does blue and yellow make?
蓝黄色
Blellow.
你们得搞定这事
You need to fix this.
我整晚都睡不着
I could not sleep all night
想着那些讨厌的人们
thinking about those obnoxious people
要住在我们隔壁
living next door to us.
特别是那个穿着破洞牛仔裤 留着长发
Especially that boy with the ripped jeans and the long hair
叫我辣妹的蓝眼睛男生
and those blue eyes who called me hot.
我 辣妹 开什么玩笑
Me? Hot? What?
菲尔 糟糕的邻居会毁掉你的一生
Phil, you know a bad neighbor can ruin your whole life.
你记得我瑜伽课上认识的朋友朱丽叶吧
You remember my friend Juliet from yoga class?
我们去过她哥哥的餐馆
We went to her brother's restaurant.
戴成人牙套的
Adult braces.
不记得
Nope.
黑色的
Black.
朱丽叶 她怎么样
Juliet. How is she?
惨透了
Miserable.
她家隔壁搬来了糟糕的邻居
These awful people moved in next door to her,
她感觉被困在了房子里
and she feels like she's trapped in her house.
她每天早上得跑到自己车上
She has to run to her car every morning.
-怪不得她小腿肌肉发达 -菲尔
- That explains those calves. - Phil.
那我应该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
我这有一份报价 比要价高很多
I have one offer, and it's way above asking.
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
也许 是否有可能
Maybe, isn't it possible
杰瑞根本就没看过这份报价
that Jerry never even sees this offer?
东西有时候无缘无故就不见了
Things do go missing all the time.
我在法律上有义务把所有报价都提供给他
I'm legally bound to present all offers.
-你懂的嘛 -不要再这样说了
- Wink, wink. - Stop doing that.
隐瞒信息是违反地产经纪人的
Withholding information would be a violation
入职宣誓的
of the realtor's oath.
那宣誓是你自己写的
Which you wrote.
我的结婚誓词也是自己写的
Well, I also wrote my own wedding vows.
我干脆连那也一起违反吧
I guess I should break those, too?
菲尔
Phil.
看我胡说什么呢
What am I saying?
每晚睡前我都会给你一个拥抱
I'll never send you to bed without a hug.
曼尼起来了吗
Manny up yet?
他在穿衣服 怎么了
He's getting dressed. Why?
昨晚我回来的时候他已经睡了
He was asleep when I got home last night.
我要跟他谈谈索菲和厄尔的问题
And I want to talk to him about the Sophie-Earl situation.
你又要再来一次吗
Are you going to start again?
我已经受够了听你唠叨
I am tired of hearing you rant
疯狂的衣柜界的事了
about the crazy closet world.
我为什么要唠叨"疯狂的衣柜界"呢
Why would I rant about crazy closet world?
那家公司早就因为定价过高而没有销路了
Those lunatics priced themselves out of business years ago.
曼尼
Manny?!
两分钟就好 我在整理服装
Two minutes! I'm fixing my costume!
他想不想跟那个女孩约会
If he wants to date this girl,
都跟你没有关系
it's none of your business.
这正是我要对他说的话
That's exactly what I was gonna tell him.
杰在哪里
Where's Jay?
你来这干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
我们之间的矛盾有些失控了
This thing between us is getting out of control.
现在必须做个了结
We got to put an end to it right now.
除非你愿意承担30年前你所做的事
As long as you own up to what you did 30 years ago.
如果我道歉
If apologizing
能让你那邪恶的儿子离我的索菲远点
is gonna keep your no-good son away from my Sophie, then --
他才不是邪恶的
He's not a no-good!
没错 他是 他就是个行走的荷尔蒙
Yes, he is. He's a walking hormone.
现在听他道歉
Now, let's hear this apology.
好吧
Fine.
那个时候我承受的压力很大 而且
I was under a lot of pressure back then, and -
好了 要记住我还没有化妆
Okay, keep in mind I'm not in makeup yet,
这凉鞋是不是让我的腿显得很粗
but do these sandals make my legs look thick?
如果是的话 我可以把裙边卷下去
'Cause I -- I could lower the hem.
天哪
Aw, geez.
他是谁
Who's that?
他是 是女佣的儿子
That's, uh, the maid's son.
等会儿再说 戈麦斯
Not now, Gomez!
杰 你在干什么
Jay, what are you doing?!
让他把话说完
Letting the man speak!
真抱歉 我不知道有客人来了
I'm sorry, I didn't know we had any company.
你好 我是曼尼
Hi. I'm Manny.
你就是曼尼
You're Manny?
你刚才说你当时压力很大...
You said you were under pressure...
他就是那个对我的索菲
This is the big stud
毛手毛脚的大种马吗
who's been groping my Sophie?
先生 我向您保证
Sir, I promise you
我和索菲之间没什么见不得人的事
there's nothing untoward between me and Sophie.
你知道吗 孩子
You know what, kid?
我相信你
I believe you.
你应该相信
And you should.
他是这世界上最善良的男孩
He's the sweetest boy in the whole world!
不 他不是
No, he's not!
普里契特 真希望现在有面大号的镜子
Pritchett, I wish I had a number-10 mirror
让你看看你现在的表情
so you could see the look on your face right now.
这个真不错
Hey, this is nice.
我想我会叫它"摇滚袜袜"
I think I am gonna call it the "sock 'n' roll."
去你的吧
The hell you are.
该死 那名字真不错
Damn! That's a good name.
你好 菲尔 快请进
Hey, Phil. Come on in.
你好 杰瑞
Hey, Jerry.
这单身公寓真不错啊
Well, look at this bachelor pad.
是啊
Yeah.
附近这一带挺有意思的
And what a fun neighborhood you live in.
你锁好车了吧
H-hey, you locked up your car, right?
-确定锁了 -很好
- I definitely did, yeah. - Good.
要喝点茶吗
Hey, you want some tea?
我只有一个锅
This is my only pot,
所以可能会有点奶酪通心粉在里面
so it might be a little macaroni-and-cheesy.
不用了 我不吃碳水化合物
I'm good. I'm cutting carbs.
你看那份报价了吗
So, did you, uh, get a chance to look over that offer?
是的 很不错
Yeah, it's great.
我终于可以搬到个好一点的地方了
I can finally move into a better place,
说不定还够钱做那个
maybe get that colonoscopy
医生强烈建议的结肠镜检查
my doctor's been pushing for.
要是我告诉你
What if I told you
还有更高的报价呢
there's an even better offer coming?
有吗
There is?
当然可能会有了
There sure might be!
明天可能会有人出更高的价钱
Tomorrow, someone could show up and offer way more.
可是 菲尔 这已经比我的要价高了
But, Phil, this is above asking.
你为什么不希望我接受它呢
Why don't you want me to take it?
就是有种不好的感觉
Oh, just a bad feeling.
你是不是有事瞒着我
Are you not telling me something?
没有 就是...有种不好的感觉
Nope, that's just the f-- the bad feeling.
那就好 因为现在你是我
Good, because you're the only one
-唯一可以相信的人 -该死
- I can trust these days. - Damn it!
这家人看起来不像好人
These new buyers just seem like terrible people.
我知道这样很自私 但我们只是
I know it's selfish, but we just --
我们不希望他们住在隔壁
We don't want them living next door to us.
没关系 我明白
No, I get it.
隔壁那家的人
The guys on the other side of this wall,
他们喜欢喝醉酒后玩射钉枪
they like to get drunk and play with their nail gun.
太疯狂了吧
Oh, that's...crazy.
听着 菲尔
Listen, Phil.
你一直都是我的好邻居 好朋友
You've always been a great neighbor and a good friend.
我想我可以再等等
I think I can hold out a little longer on the offer.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的
Yeah.
我是那种看到瓶子一半满着的乐观人士
I think of this old pickle jar as being half full.
好烫
Hot!
就没有什么好事会轮到我
I can't have anything nice.
别站在墙边
Not the wall!
我发誓 我会帮助
On my honor, I promise to
有需要人士找到合适的住所
aid in man's quest for shelter,
我会记得我不仅是在做房产生意
to recognize I'm not just in the business of houses --
更重要的是寄托在房屋上的梦想
I'm in the business of dreams in the shape of houses.
你们小心点
Hey! Careful with that!
这可是艺术品
It's art.
真不敢相信这是真的
I can't believe this is happening.
也许没那么糟
Who knows?
也许最后我们会爱上他们
Maybe we'll end up loving 'em.
是啊 可能吧
Yeah. Maybe.
保证不隐瞒所有违法事件
To disclose all illegal additions,
包括豆腐渣工程 凶杀案 或是闹鬼
shoddy construction, murders, and ghosts...
是我们多心了
Are we wrong
还是我们四个之间的气氛的确有些微妙
or is there some tension between the four of us?
可能有点吧
Uh, maybe a little.
可能有点
Maybe a little.
-我说对了吧 -没错
- I told ya. - Yeah.
好吧 那么
All right. Well...
我们随时恭候
We're up for it whenever you are.
你懂的
Wink, wink.
把客户的利益摆在我的利益之上
...and to put my clients' needs before my own.
还有我的
And mine.
看来有人提前需要睡前抱抱了
Someone needs her bedtime hug early.
是啊 来吧
Yep. Come here.
-普兰克老师好 -普兰克老师好
- Hi, Ms. Plank. - Hey, Ms. Plank.
这不是玛丽安和小姜姐妹俩嘛
Well, well, well, if it isn't Mary Ann and Ginger.
真幽默
That's hilarious.
是啊 因为...
Okay. 'cause --
-是啊 -真有趣
- Yeah. Oh. - Oh, that's funny.
但是
And while
既然说到好笑的事了
while we're laughing about things,
还有件事很好笑
uh, this is funny, too.
我们之前好像没有跟莉莉谈过
It seems that we forgot to talk to Lily
就过来找您了
before coming in to see you.
她的态度很明确 毫不犹豫
And -- and she made it very clear in no uncertain terms
她很喜欢您
that she loves you,
她希望可以留在您的班上
and she wants to stay in your class.
这多好呀是不是
How -- how great is that?
我愿意让莉莉回来
I will take Lily back...
只要你们能回答我
...if you are able to tell me
这句话的宾语[目的]是什么
the object of this sentence --
天哪
Oh, gosh.
"莉莉的家长看错普兰克老师了"
"Lily's parents were wrong about Mrs. Plank."
你知道是什么吗
Do you know it?
我想 这句话的目的是要羞辱我们
I -- I -- I think that the object is to humiliate us?
答对了 你们看
Correct. See?
什么人我都能教
I can teach anybody.